Guide to the Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 4. Office Administration Files, 1962-2010 TJU.2010.01.04
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Office Management, 1981-2001; III.
  - High-level recommendations, 1984-1985 (Box 685, Folder 8)
  - High-level recommendations, 1986-1988 (Box 685, Folder 9)
  - High-level recommendations, 1988 (Box 685, Folder 10)
  - Intern information, 1981 (Box 685, Folder 11)
  - Legislative correspondent test, 1983 (Box 685, Folder 12)
  - Library of Congress, 1980s (Box 685, Folder 13)
  - Mobile office, 1996 (Box 685, Folder 14)
  - Office budget, 1981-1982 (Box 685, Folder 15)
  - Office complaints, 1993 (Box 685, Folder 16)
  - Office faxes, 1997 (Box 685, Folder 17-18)
  - Office manager responsibilities, 1981 (Box 685, Folder 19)
  - Office policy manuals, 1985-1991 (Box 685, Folder 20)
  - Office policy manuals, 1993-1997 (Box 685, Folder 21)
  - Office of Senate Chief Counsel for Employment (OSCCE), Employment Law Reporter, 1998 (Box 685, Folder 22)
  - OSCCE, Manger's Guide to Complying with the Family and Medical Leave Act (FMLA), 1997 (Box 685, Folder 23)
  - OSCCE, Manager's Guide to Understanding Sexual Harassment in the Workplace, 1997 (Box 685, Folder 24)
  - OSCCE, Reference Guide to the Occupational Safety and Health Provisions of the Congressional Accountability Act, 1995 (Box 685, Folder 25)
  - Parking, 1994 (Box 685, Folder 26)
  - Pies, 1981-1991 (Box 685, Folder 27)
  - Pittsburgh office relocation, 1982 (Box 685, Folder 28)
  - Political recommendations, 1994 (Box 685, Folder 29)
  - Records Management Handbook, 1998 (Box 685, Folder 30)
  - Scranton office relocation, 1995 (Box 685, Folder 31)
  - Senate Office Accounting System, 1994 (Box 686, Folder 1)
  - Senate Services Directory, 2001 (Box 686, Folder 2)
  - Sexual harassment policy, 1991 (Box 686, Folder 3)
  - Sexual orientation statement, 1994 (Box 686, Folder 4)
  - Staff assignments, 1981-1984 (Box 686, Folder 5)
  - Staff office photos, undated (Box 686, Folder 6)
  - Staff office allowances, 1995 (Box 686, Folder 7)
  - Status reports, 1993-1996 (Box 686, Folder 8)
  - Thursday lunches, 1981 (Box 686, Folder 9)
  - VIP tours, 1990 (Box 686, Folder 10)
  - VIP tours, 1991 (Box 686, Folder 11)
- Telephone Logs, 1981-1986; IV.
  Telephone Logs contains records detailing incoming calls to Senator Specter's office from 1981 through 1986. This series is arranged chronologically.
  - January 1981-July 1981 (Box 687)
  - March 1981-November 1981 (Box 688)
  - March 1981-January 1982 (Box 689)
  - January 1982-September 1982 (Box 690)
  - August 1982-January 1983 (Box 691)
  - May 1983-February 1985 (Box 692)
  - February 1985-June 1985 (Box 693)
  - June 1985-March 1986 (Box 694)
  - April 1986-August 1986 (Box 695)
  - August 1986-September 1986 (Box 696)
- Trip Files, 1981-2010; V.
  Trip Files includes informations on foreign and domestic trips taken by Senator Specter. Foreign travel was most often as part of a Congressional delegation (CODEL), and focuses on destinations like the Middle East, Western Europe and eastern Asia. Domestic trips primarily focus on Pennsylvania, as Specter was known for making a point of regularly visiting each county. This series is arranged chronologically, and contains itineraries, reports, photos, and background material on destinations.
  - International trips, 1981-2010; 1.
    - Europe, North Atlantic Assembly, 1981 (Box 697, Folder 1)
    - Trip administration, 1981-1996 (Box 697, Folder 2-3)
    - Europe, North Atlantic Assembly, 1982 (Box 697, Folder 4)
    - Tokyo, Hong Kong, New Zealand, Australia, January 1982 (Box 697, Folder 5)
    - Netherlands, North Atlantic Assembly, Portugal, International Court of Justice, February-November 1982 (Box 697, Folder 6)
    - West Germany, May 1982 (Box 697, Folder 7)
    - USSR, July 1982 (Box 697, Folder 8-9)
    - Middle East, Israel, September 1982 (Box 697, Folder 10-11)
    - England, Switzerland, Spain, Portugal, November 1982 (Box 697, Folder 12-13)
    - Geneva, October 1982-December 1983 (Box 697, Folder 14)
    - Mexico, Brazil, Peru, March-April 1983 (Box 697, Folder 15)
    - El Salvador, May 1983 (Box 697, Folder 16-17)
    - Israel, Egypt, Rome, Copenhagen, May-June 1983 (Box 697, Folder 18)
    - Central America, August 1983 (Box 697, Folder 19)
    - Europe, November-December 1983 (Box 697, Folder 20)
    - Travel requests to embassies, 1983-1989 (Box 697, Folder 21)
    - China, Taiwan, Hong Kong, January 1984 (Box 697, Folder 22-25)
    - Cambridge, February 1984 (Box 698, Folder 1)
    - International Court of Justice, May 1984 (Box 698, Folder 2)
    - Middle East, August 1984 (Box 698, Folder 3)
    - Europe, North Atlantic Assembly, Conferences, November 1984 (Box 698, Folder 4-5)
    - Central America, April 1986 (Box 698, Folder 6-7)
    - Turkey, North Atlantic Assembly, November 1986 (Box 698, Folder 8)
    - Foreign Travel Records, November 1986 - May 1991 (Box 698, Folder 9)
    - Frankfurt, Israel, Egypt, Kuwait, January 1987 (Box 698, Folder 10-13)
    - Geneva Arms Talk, February-March 1987 (Box 698, Folder 14)
    - Europe and Morocco, April 1987 (Box 698, Folder 15-17)
    - Quebec, North Atlantic Assembly, May 1987 (Box 698, Folder 18)
    - Geneva, Senate Arms Control Observer Group, June 1987 (Box 698, Folder 19-20)
    - Congressional Record, Foreign travel, July 1987-March 1988 (Box 698, Folder 21)
    - International Trips Administration, 1987-1989 (Box 698, Folder 22)
    - Europe and Middle East, January 1988 (Box 698, Folder 23-26)
    - Europe and Middle East, January 1988 (Box 699, Folder 1-7)
    - Portugal, North Atlantic Assembly, March 1988 (Box 699, Folder 8)
    - North Africa and Middle East, April 1988 (Box 699, Folder 9-11)
    - Latin America, August-September 1988 (Box 699, Folder 12-17)
    - Asia, November 1988 (Box 700, Folder 1-2)
    - Congressional Record, Foreign travel, July 1988-June 1989 (Box 700, Folder 3)
    - Middle East, Hungary, Greece, January 1989 (Box 700, Folder 4-11)
    - Brazil and Venezuela, March-April 1989 (Box 700, Folder 12-16)
    - Brazil and Venezuela, March - April 1989 (Box 701, Folder 1)
    - Turkey, North Atlantic Assembly, May 1989 (Box 701, Folder 2)
    - Yugoslavia, Soviet Union, Algiers, August-September 1989 (Box 701, Folder 3-6)
    - Congressional Record, Foreign travel, June 1989-October 1990 (Box 701, Folder 7)
    - Russia, India, Middle East, Saddam Hussein, January 1990 (Box 701, Folder 8-12)
    - Latin America, April 1990 (Box 701, Folder 13-18)
    - Europe and Morocco, Aspen Institute, August 1990 (Box 702, Folder 1-4)
    - Passport, 1990-1993 (Box 702, Folder 5)
    - England, Belgium, North Atlantic Assembly, November 1992 (Box 702, Folder 6)
    - Foreign gifts, January 1993 (Box 702, Folder 7)
    - Middle East, Croatia, February 1993 (Box 702, Folder 8-12)
    - Africa, April 1993 (Box 702, Folder 13-18)
    - Denmark, North Atlantic Assembly, Russia, Ireland, October 1993 (Box 702, Folder 19-20)
    - China, Hong Kong, November 1993 (Box 703, Folder 1-2)
    - Cairo, Amman, Damascus, Israel, December 1993 (Box 703, Folder 3-6)
    - Trip photos, 1993 (Box 703, Folder 7)
    - Travel administration, 1994 (Box 703, Folder 8)
    - Asia, January 1994 (Box 703, Folder 9-11)
    - Mexico, April 1994 (Box 703, Folder 12)
    - Oslo, Russia, Kazakhstan, Kyrgystan, Uzbekistan, Turkmenistan, World War II anniversary trip, June 1994 (Box 703, Folder 13-17)
    - Latin America, May 1995 (Box 703, Folder 18-19)
    - Latin America, May 1995 (Box 704, Folder 1-2)
    - Asia, Middle East, Bulgaria, Belgium, August-September 1995 (Box 704, Folder 3-7)
    - Africa, Israel, Netherlands, December 1995-January 1996 (Box 704, Folder 8-14)
    - France, Croatia, Bosnia, Serbia, The Hauge, April 1996 (Box 704, Folder 15-17)
    - Korea Trip, June - July 1996 (Box 704, Folder 18)
    - Asia, Middle East, France, August 1996 (Box 705, Folder 1-4)
    - Europe, November 1996 (Box 705, Folder 5)
    - The Hauge, Sarajevo, The Middle East, Sudan, Eritrea, Italy, December 1997-January 1998 (Box 705, Folder 6-9)
    - Europe, Middle East, India, Pakistan, December 1998 (Box 705, Folder 10-11)
    - Middle East, The Hauge, Ukraine, Italy, December 1998-August 1999 (Box 705, Folder 12-14)
    - Cuba, June 1999 (Box 705, Folder 15-17)
    - Middle East and Europe, August 1999 (Box 706, Folder 1-3)
    - Key West, Panama, Colombia, December 1999 (Box 706, Folder 4)
    - Comprehensive travel list, 1999 (Box 706, Folder 5)
    - Travel Administration, 1999-2000 (Box 706, Folder 6)
    - Morocco, Italy, Kosovo, Tunisia, Turkey, Israel, Jordan, January 2000 (Box 706, Folder 7-10)
    - Syria, June 2000 (Box 706, Folder 11)
    - Africa, August 2000 (Box 706, Folder 12-14)
    - Europe, Middle East, India, Pakistan, December 2000-January 2001 (Box 706, Folder 15-18)
    - London, Florence, Tel Aviv, Ashkelon, Jerusalem, Cairo, Damascus, Rome, April 2001 (Box 706, Folder 19)
    - China, Taiwan, Korea, Hawaii, August 2001 (Box 707, Folder 1)
    - Travel administration, 2001 (Box 707, Folder 2)
    - Latin America, January 2000 (Box 707, Folder 3)
    - Europe and Middle East, March-April 2002 (Box 707, Folder 4)
    - Brazil, Africa, Italy, August 2002 (Box 707, Folder 5)
    - Europe and Middle East, December 2002 - January 2003 (Box 707, Folder 6-7)
    - Latin America, August 2005 (Box 707, Folder 8)
    - Middle East, December 2005 (Box 707, Folder 9)
    - South America, April 2006 (Box 707, Folder 10)
    - Netherlands, Belgium, France, Tunisia, May-June 2006 (Box 707, Folder 11)
    - China, Tibet, India, Kuwait, Israel, Libya, August 2006 (Box 707, Folder 12)
    - United Kingdom, India, Syria, Israel, Italy, December 2006 (Box 707, Folder 13)
    - United Kingdom, Belgium, Poland, Russia, Turkey, Finland, France, August 2007 (Box 707, Folder 14)
    - United Kingdom, Israel, Pakistan, Syria, Jordan, Austria, Belgium, France, December 2007-January 2008 (Box 707, Folder 15)
    - Latin America, August 2008 (Box 707, Folder 16)
    - United Kingdom, Israel, Syria, Austria, Belgium, Norway, Iceland, December 2008-January 2009 (Box 707, Folder 17)
    - Cyprus, Syria, India, Afghanistan, Morocco, December 2009-January 2010 (Box 707, Folder 18)
    - United Kingdom, Czech Republic, Israel, Syria, Croatia, France, July 2010 (Box 707, Folder 19)
    - China, Vietnam, Taiwan, August 2010 (Box 707, Folder 20)
  - Domestic trips, 1983-2008; 2.
    - Philadelphia: One-day trips, 1983-1992 (Box 707, Folder 21-25)
    - Texas: Cable television, June 12-15, 1983 (Box 707, Folder 26)
    - Florida, March 23-25, 1984 (Box 707, Folder 27)
    - Pennsylvania, February 1986 (Box 707, Folder 28-29)
    - Canada, U.S. Interparliamentary Group, February 27-March 3, 1986 (Box 707, Folder 30)
    - Alaska, July 1988 (Box 707, Folder 31)
    - New Orleans: Republican National Convention, August 15-18, 1988 (Box 707, Folder 32)
    - Room confirmations, Fall 1988 (Box 707, Folder 33)
    - California, October 1988 (Box 707, Folder 34)
    - Harrisburg, Lancaster: Health Care, February 17-18, 1989 (Box 707, Folder 35)
    - Hershey, Pottsville: Town hall meetings, August 8, 1989 (Box 707, Folder 36)
    - Harrisburg, York, Lancaster: School visits, September 25, 1989 (Box 708, Folder 1)
    - Harrisburg, Camp Hill: High school, Prison, October 30, 1989 (Box 708, Folder 2)
    - Pottsville, Bloomsburg, Sunbury, Lewistown, Port Royal, Harrisburg, December 1-4, 1989 (Box 708, Folder 3)
    - Media, Coatesville, Lancaster, Philadelphia, December 12, 1989 (Box 708, Folder 4)
    - Travel administration, 1989-1992 (Box 708, Folder 5)
    - Dauphin County, Lancaster: Health, Steelworkers Convention, February 5, 1990 (Box 708, Folder 6)
    - Williamsport, State College, February 19, 1990 (Box 708, Folder 7)
    - Allentown, Hazelton, Pottsville, Wayne: Drug Abuse, February 26, 1990 (Box 708, Folder 8)
    - Schuylkill County, Lancaster County, Pittsburgh, April 23, 1990 (Box 708, Folder 9)
    - Allentown, Orefield, Hamburg, Pottsville, Reading, April 30, 1990 (Box 708, Folder 10)
    - Harrisburg Hospital, May-June 1990 (Box 708, Folder 11)
    - Camp Hill Prison, US Army War College, June 11, 1990 (Box 708, Folder 12)
    - Bloomsburg: Republican State Committee, June 25, 1990 (Box 708, Folder 13)
    - Central Pennsylvania: Open houses, July 2, 1990 (Box 708, Folder 14)
    - Dauphin County, York County, Lancaster: Open house, American Legion, July 14, 1990 (Box 708, Folder 15)
    - Hershey Trade Convention, August 15, 1990 (Box 708, Folder 16)
    - Lancaster, York, Harrisburg: Spanish/Hispanic outreach, August 21-28, 1990 (Box 708, Folder 17)
    - Lancaster, Harrisburg: Poultry, SEPTA, September 24, 1990 (Box 708, Folder 18)
    - Dauphin and Cumberland Counties: GOP Dinners, October 9, 1990 (Box 708, Folder 19)
    - Travel schedules, October 1990 (Box 708, Folder 20)
    - Reading, Springfield, Newtown Square, Philadelphia: Open houses, November 5, 1990 (Box 708, Folder 21)
    - Lancaster, Harrisburg: Local legislative initiatives, December 11, 1990 (Box 708, Folder 22)
    - Middletown, Lancaster, Harrisburg: Farms, February 4, 1991 (Box 708, Folder 23)
    - Dauphin County, Harrisburg: Town meeting, Republican State Committee, February 22, 1991 (Box 708, Folder 24)
    - Harrisburg, Middletown, Lancaster: HARSCO, Airport, February 25, 1991 (Box 708, Folder 25)
    - Harrisburg: Pennsylvania Steelworkers, AFL-CIO, March 18, 1991 (Box 708, Folder 26)
    - SEPTA Airport, Harrisburg, Pittsburgh, March 22, 1991 (Box 708, Folder 27)
    - Lebanon, Coatesville: Open Houses, DADDS March, March 23, 1991 (Box 708, Folder 28)
    - Schuylkill County, April 1, 1991 (Box 708, Folder 29)
    - Central Pennsylvania: Child Care, Health Care, April 3, 1991 (Box 708, Folder 30)
    - Penn State Altoona, April 1991 (Box 708, Folder 31)
    - Lancaster, Philadelphia, Springfield: AT&T, Navy Yard, Delaware County Republicans, May 13, 1991 (Box 708, Folder 32)
    - Clarion County: Open house, May 30, 1991 (Box 708, Folder 33)
    - Grove Worldwide: Veterans, May-June 1991 (Box 708, Folder 34)
    - Somerset, Bedford: Open houses, June 1-2, 1991 (Box 708, Folder 35)
    - Western Pennsylvania: Open houses, Meetings, July 1-3, 1991 (Box 708, Folder 36)
    - Warminster, Philadelphia, Etters: Community leaders, Farms, July 22, 1991 (Box 708, Folder 37)
    - Eastern Pennsylvania: Army, DnyCorp, Senior Citizens, August 7, 1991 (Box 708, Folder 38)
    - State College, Erie: Open house, Agriculture, AG Progress Days, August 13, 1991 (Box 708, Folder 39)
    - Camp Hill Prison, August 21, 1991 (Box 708, Folder 40)
    - Philadelphia, Tinicum: University of Pennsylania, SEPTA, Courthouse, September 23, 1991 (Box 708, Folder 41)
    - Hershey: Press conferences, September 30, 1991 (Box 708, Folder 42)
    - Minersville, Pottsville, Reading: Prison, Steering group, Highways, October 7, 1991 (Box 708, Folder 43)
    - Wormleysburg, Harrisburg, Lancaster: Veterans, Republican Caucus, Yachts, October 8, 1991 (Box 708, Folder 44)
    - Lebanon: Veterans, November 12, 1991 (Box 708, Folder 45)
    - Landsdowne, Narvon, Lancaster: Environment, December 2, 1991 (Box 708, Folder 46)
    - Central Pennsylvania: SETCO, Schools, December 17-18, 1991 (Box 708, Folder 47)
    - Lancaster, York, Adams, Fulton, and Huntingdon Counties: Open houses, County leaders, January 9, 1992 (Box 708, Folder 48)
    - Perry County, Harrisburg, Lancaster County: Open house, Republicans, January 20, 1992 (Box 708, Folder 49)
    - Central Pennsylvania: County Republicans, February 21, 1992 (Box 708, Folder 50)
    - Waynesboro, Shippensburg, Harrisburg, Lancaster Jail: Endorsement, Local government, March 6, 1992 (Box 708, Folder 51)
    - Wormleysburg, Lancaster, Philadelphia: Veterans, Police, Firefighters, March 16, 1992 (Box 708, Folder 52)
    - Central and Eastern Pennsylvania: Ferry, PRL Industries, Republicans, March 20, 1992 (Box 708, Folder 53)
    - Central Pennsylvania: Media, Day care, Airport, April 3-6, 1992 (Box 708, Folder 54)
    - Erie, Tobyhanna, Philadelphia: City Hall, Seniors, AT&T, April 21, 1992 (Box 709, Folder 1)
    - New Cumberland, Central Pennsylvania: Veterans, Congressman Walker, April 22-24, 1992 (Box 709, Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania Cities: Navy yard, Press conferences, Rallies, April 27, 1992 (Box 709, Folder 3)
    - Hershey: Pennsylvanians for Effective Government (PEG) dinner, May 12, 1992 (Box 709, Folder 4)
    - Harrisburg: Hospital, Republican State Committee, June 5-6, 1992 (Box 709, Folder 5)
    - Hershey, Harrisburg: Caucus, George Bloom, Conference of Teamsters, June 8, 1992 (Box 709, Folder 6)
    - Monroeville, Harrisburg, Chambersburg: American Legion, League of Cities, Women, Republican Committee, July 9, 1992 (Box 709, Folder 7)
    - Central and Eastern Pennsylvania: Labor, Steering, Business, Prison, July 15, 1992 (Box 709, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh, Harrisburg, Gettysburg: County Commissioners, PSEA, August 3, 1992 (Box 709, Folder 9)
    - New Cumberland: UAW Cap Council, August 11, 1992 (Box 709, Folder 10)
    - Philadelphia, Mechanicsburg, Harrisburg, Hershey: Teachers, Navy, Women, Trades convention, August 17, 1992 (Box 709, Folder 11)
    - Lancaster, Philadelphia, Pittsburgh: Hospital, Republican Committee, Aviation, September 9, 1992 (Box 709, Folder 12)
    - Harrisburg, Mt. Joy, Myerstown, Pittsburgh, Robesonia: Republican Committee, September 19, 1992 (Box 709, Folder 13)
    - Philadelphia, New Cumberland, Harrisburg, York, October 5, 1992 (Box 709, Folder 14)
    - Lancaster, York, Chambersburg, Greensburg: Fundraiser, Hospital, October 9, 1992 (Box 709, Folder 15)
    - Erie, Reynoldsville, Harrisburg, Avoca, Wilkes-Barre, Pittston: Fundraisers, Veterans, Farms, October 21, 1992 (Box 709, Folder 16)
    - Pittsburgh, Philadelphia, Hershey, Lancaster: Hospitals, GOP dinner, October 22, 1992 (Box 709, Folder 17)
    - Pottstown, Reading, Hazelton, Lewisburg: Mine Workers, CAS, October 24, 1992 (Box 709, Folder 18)
    - Lancaster, York, Carlisle, Dauphin, Philadelphia, October 27, 1992 (Box 709, Folder 19)
    - Pittsburgh, Erie, Harrisburg: Radio, Navy, Fundraiser, October 29, 1992 (Box 709, Folder 20)
    - Philadelphia, Harrisburg, Johnstown, Pittsburgh, Erie, Allentown, November 2, 1992 (Box 709, Folder 21)
    - Pittsburgh, Middletown, Bethlehem, Avoca, Pittston, Harrisburg, February 19, 1993 (Box 709, Folder 22)
    - Harrisburg, Hillside: Drug Enforcement, Fundraisers, Lumber, April 26, 1993 (Box 709, Folder 23)
    - Mechanicsburg: Business, Government, and Community Leaders, May 26, 1993 (Box 709, Folder 24)
    - Ohio, Wisconsin: Speeches, June 1, 1993 (Box 709, Folder 25)
    - Harrisburg, Hershey, McKees Rocks, Erie: Teamsters, PNC, June 7, 1993 (Box 709, Folder 26)
    - Harrisburg, September 10-11, 1993 (Box 709, Folder 27)
    - Harrisburg: Business Leaders, Media, Endorsement, September 27, 1993 (Box 709, Folder 28)
    - Chicago: Republican Majority Coalition, October 25, 1993 (Box 709, Folder 29)
    - Wilkes-Barre, Summerdale, Harrisburg: Guns, December 22, 1993 (Box 709, Folder 30-33)
    - Electronic town meeting, February 14, 1994 (Box 709, Folder 34)
    - Boston, June 9, 1994 (Box 709, Folder 35)
    - Dauphin, Lebanon: Township supervisors, Medical society, April 18, 1994 (Box 709, Folder 36)
    - Harrisburg: YWCA, Domestic violence, July 11, 1994 (Box 709, Folder 37)
    - Dauphin: Healthcare, August 1, 1994 (Box 709, Folder 38)
    - Harrisburg: Republican State Committee, Crime issues, September 9-10, 1994 (Box 709, Folder 39)
    - Dauphin, Lackawanna, Luzerne: Board meeting, Friends Luncheon, November 4, 1994 (Box 709, Folder 40)
    - Iowa, Harrisburg: Press conferences, Gubernatorial inauguration, January 16-17, 1995 (Box 709, Folder 41)
    - Tobyhanna Army Depot, Harrisburg, Mechanicsburg: Business, Government, Military, Community leaders, February 6, 1995 (Box 709, Folder 42)
    - Philadelphia, Hershey: Elsie Hillman, Republican State Committee, February 11, 1995 (Box 709, Folder 43)
    - Central and Eastern Pennsylvania: Rite Aid, SPCC, Aviation, Army, Navy, February 27, 1995 (Box 709, Folder 44)
    - State College, Letterkenny, Chambersburg: TV taping, Press conference, March 13, 1995 (Box 709, Folder 45)
    - Philadelphia, Harrisburg: Rittenhouse Courthouse, Bankers speech, March 20, 1995 (Box 709, Folder 46)
    - Washington DC, Harrisburg, New Hampshire, Maryland, Iowa, Kansas: Presidential bid, March 30 - April 1, 1995 (Box 709, Folder 47)
    - Delaware, Camp Hill, Harrisburg: Prisons, April 3, 1995 (Box 709, Folder 48)
    - Hazelton, Hershey, Danville: Teamsters, Radio, Hospital, June 5, 1995 (Box 709, Folder 49)
    - Pittsburgh, Harrisburg, Philadelphia: Juvenile crime, Press conference, September 18, 1995 (Box 709, Folder 50)
    - Hershey, Harrisburg: Hate crimes, November 20, 1995 (Box 710, Folder 1)
    - Avoca, Altoona: Editorial boards, Citizens Voice, November 27, 1995 (Box 710, Folder 2)
    - York, Lancaster, State College: Press, Board meetings, Campaign, November 27 - December 2, 1995 (Box 710, Folder 3)
    - Harrisburg: Business and industry meeting (cancelled), High school, December 18, 1995 (Box 710, Folder 4)
    - Chambersburg, Gettysburg, Hershey, Harrisburg: Town meetings, February 9-10, 1996 (Box 710, Folder 5)
    - Allentown, Reading, Lancaster: Town meetings, March 2, 1996 (Box 710, Folder 6)
    - Harrisburg, Wormleysburg, Lebanon, York: Town meetings, March 25, 1996 (Box 710, Folder 7)
    - Harrisburg, Hershey: PSEA, Dole reception, April 10, 1996 (Box 710, Folder 8)
    - Philadelphia, Bucks, Chester, Lancaster Counties: CAS, GOP, Drugs, April 12, 1996 (Box 710, Folder 9)
    - Sunbury, Bloomsburg, Bethlehem, Rydal: Town meetings, April 13, 1996 (Box 710, Folder 10)
    - AMP meet and greet, April 15, 1996 (Box 710, Folder 11)
    - Dauphin, Schuylkill Counties, Washington DC: Town meeting, Children, April, 22, 1996 (Box 710, Folder 12)
    - Hershey, Wilkes-Barre: Business leaders, Mass transit, June 3, 1996 (Box 710, Folder 13)
    - Harrisburg, Hershey: Attorneys, Republican reception, June 7-8, 1996 (Box 710, Folder 14)
    - Lancaster, Lititz, Pittsburgh, Philadelphia: Mass transit, Postmasters, Junes 17, 1996 (Box 710, Folder 15)
    - Gettysburg, Chambersburg, Philadelphia: Women, Hospital, Press, June 21, 1996 (Box 710, Folder 16)
    - Central and Eastern Pennsylvania: Town meetings, Elected officials, July 1-2, 1996 (Box 710, Folder 17)
    - Delaware, Lancaster, Luzerne, Lackawanna Counties: Abstinence, July 29, 1996 (Box 710, Folder 18)
    - Harrisburg: Abstinence, Fred Anton, Republican State Committee, September 20, 1996 (Box 710, Folder 19)
    - Cumberland and Dauphin: Women Republicans, September 21, 1996 (Box 710, Folder 20)
    - Lancaster, Cumberland, and York Counties: DDRE, High schools, Rally, October 2, 1996 (Box 710, Folder 21)
    - Harrisburg, Philadelphia: Domestic violence, School district, Roundtable, October 9, 1996 (Box 710, Folder 22)
    - Harrisburg, Pittsburgh, Scranton: Airport press conferences, November 2, 1996 (Box 710, Folder 23)
    - Harrisburg: Drugs, Governor Ridge, November 25, 1996 (Box 710, Folder 24)
    - Harrisburg: Pennsylvania inaugurations, January 21, 1997 (Box 710, Folder 25)
    - York, Adams County, Wormleysburg, Harrisburg, Hershey: Prison, Veterans, February 7, 1996 (Box 710, Folder 26)
    - Camp Hill, Williamsport: Rite Aid, CAS, Hospital administrators, March 24, 1997 (Box 710, Folder 27)
    - York County Prison, Adams, Cumberland, Dauphin, Hershey: Veterans, February 7-8, 1997 (Box 710, Folder 28)
    - Northumberland, Montour, Lehigh, Columbia, Montgomery Counties: GOP Breakfast, High schools, Farms, March 25, 1997 (Box 710, Folder 29)